[
{ "id": 1, "front": "aandoen", "back": "(hebben) aangedaan" },
{ "id": 2, "front": "aankomen", "back": "(zijn) aangekomen" },
{ "id": 3, "front": "antwoorden", "back": "(hebben) geantwoord" },
{ "id": 4, "front": "bakken", "back": "(hebben) gebakken" },
{ "id": 5, "front": "beginnen", "back": "(zijn) begonnen" },
{ "id": 6, "front": "bellen", "back": "(hebben) gebeld" },
{ "id": 7, "front": "betalen", "back": "(hebben) betaald" },
{ "id": 8, "front": "bezoeken", "back": "(hebben) bezocht" },
{ "id": 9, "front": "blijven", "back": "(zijn) gebleven" },
{ "id": 10, "front": "brengen", "back": "(hebben) gebracht" },
{ "id": 11, "front": "breken", "back": "(hebben) gebroken" },
{ "id": 12, "front": "dansen", "back": "(hebben) gedanst" },
{ "id": 13, "front": "denken", "back": "(hebben) gedacht" },
{ "id": 14, "front": "doen", "back": "(hebben) gedaan" },
{ "id": 15, "front": "drinken", "back": "(hebben) gedronken" },
{ "id": 16, "front": "eten", "back": "(hebben) gegeten" },
{ "id": 17, "front": "gaan", "back": "(zijn) gegaan" },
{ "id": 18, "front": "geven", "back": "(hebben) gegeven" },
{ "id": 19, "front": "halen", "back": "(hebben) gehaald" },
{ "id": 20, "front": "hebben", "back": "(hebben) gehad" },
{ "id": 21, "front": "helpen", "back": "(hebben) geholpen" },
{ "id": 22, "front": "kiezen", "back": "(hebben) gekozen" },
{ "id": 23, "front": "kijken", "back": "(hebben)gekeken" },
{ "id": 24, "front": "koken", "back": "(hebben) gekookt" },
{ "id": 25, "front": "komen", "back": "(zijn) gekomen" },
{ "id": 26, "front": "kopen", "back": "(hebben) gekocht" },
{ "id": 27, "front": "krijgen", "back": "(hebben) gekregen" },
{ "id": 28, "front": "lachen", "back": "(hebben) gelachen" },
{ "id": 29, "front": "leggen", "back": "(hebben) gelegd" },
{ "id": 30, "front": "leren", "back": "(hebben) geleerd" },
{ "id": 31, "front": "lezen", "back": "(hebben) gelezen" },
{ "id": 32, "front": "liegen", "back": "(hebben) gelogen" },
{ "id": 33, "front": "liggen", "back": "(hebben) gelegen" },
{ "id": 34, "front": "lopen", "back": "(hebben/zijn) gelopen" },
{ "id": 35, "front": "luisteren", "back": "(hebben) geluisterd" },
{ "id": 36, "front": "maken", "back": "(hebben) gemaakt" },
{ "id": 37, "front": "nemen", "back": "(hebben) genomen" },
{ "id": 38, "front": "opruimen", "back": "(hebben) opgeruimd" },
{ "id": 39, "front": "opstaan", "back": "(zijn) opgestaan" },
{ "id": 40, "front": "poetsen", "back": "(hebben) gepoetst" },
{ "id": 41, "front": "rijden", "back": "(hebben/zijn) gereden" },
{ "id": 42, "front": "rusten", "back": "(hebben) gerust" },
{ "id": 43, "front": "schrijven", "back": "(hebben) geschreven" },
{ "id": 44, "front": "slagen", "back": "(zijn) geslaagd" },
{ "id": 45, "front": "slapen", "back": "(hebben) geslapen" },
{ "id": 46, "front": "sluiten", "back": "(hebben) gesloten" },
{ "id": 47, "front": "snijden", "back": "(hebben) gesneden" },
{ "id": 48, "front": "spelen", "back": "(hebben) gespeeld" },
{ "id": 49, "front": "spreken", "back": "(hebben) gesproken" },
{ "id": 50, "front": "stelen", "back": "(hebben) gestolen" },
{ "id": 51, "front": "sterven", "back": "(zijn) gestorven" },
{ "id": 52, "front": "stoppen", "back": "(zijn) gestopt" },
{ "id": 53, "front": "studeren", "back": "(hebben) gestudeerd" },
{ "id": 54, "front": "sturen", "back": "(hebben) gestuurd" },
{ "id": 55, "front": "telefoneren", "back": "(hebben) getelefoneerd" },
{ "id": 56, "front": "vallen", "back": "(zijn) gevallen" },
{ "id": 57, "front": "vergeten", "back": "(hebben/zijn) vergeten" },
{ "id": 58, "front": "verhuizen", "back": "(zijn) verhuisd" },
{ "id": 59, "front": "verkopen", "back": "(hebben) verkocht" },
{ "id": 60, "front": "verliezen", "back": "(hebben) verloren" },
{ "id": 61, "front": "vertrekken", "back": "(zijn) vertrokken" },
{ "id": 62, "front": "vinden", "back": "(hebben) gevonden" },
{ "id": 63, "front": "volgen", "back": "(hebben) gevolgd" },
{ "id": 64, "front": "vragen", "back": "(hebben) gevraagd" },
{ "id": 65, "front": "wachten", "back": "(hebben) gewacht" },
{ "id": 66, "front": "wandelen", "back": "(hebben/zijn) gewandeld" },
{ "id": 67, "front": "wassen", "back": "(hebben) gewassen" },
{ "id": 68, "front": "werken", "back": "(hebben) gewerkt" },
{ "id": 69, "front": "worden", "back": "(zijn) geworden" },
{ "id": 70, "front": "zeggen", "back": "(hebben) gezegd" },
{ "id": 71, "front": "zetten", "back": "(hebben) gezet" },
{ "id": 72, "front": "zien", "back": "(hebben) gezien" },
{ "id": 73, "front": "zoeken", "back": "(hebben) gezocht" },
{ "id": 74, "front": "zijn", "back": "(zijn) geweest" },
{ "id": 75, "front": "zwemmen", "back": "(hebben/zijn) gezwommen" }
]
